I shall go to the course you will be
required to take some screen prints and
see if files as well as not an existing
file saving files not an existing files
are all pretty straightforward and I'm
taking screen prints of general familiar
this is a feature that most laptops or
computers have that allows you to take a
snapshot of what's on the screen at any
given time so for example as you work
through the course you will be required
to take screenshots of certain folders
certain documents and insert them into
your assessment booklet so just a
demonstrate I'm just going to open a
folder and this is the WP to assessment
folder and I need to take a snapshot of
that so I can then insert that into the
assessment document to do that I trust
the pinata s-save on the Print Screen
button if you're using a laptop there
may be a keas that you have to hold down
the FN key to activate the Print Screen
button but if you press the Print Screen
button that will then take a snapshot
now nothing actually happens but it has
actually copied on to the clipboard you
can then go to a word document for this
office to open a blank Word document and
I can then select pierced click pierced
and that wallet insert the screenshot
into the word document so I no need to
see of this and just as an example the
file see of us and I'm going to save it
into my WP to folder because it relate
that and I will call that screen shot
[Music]
and see if that
so now for court that I folder the
screenshot one document is there double
click on that that will open back up in
wood